Yeah. Although, yeah, I could see that
through the first arrest even. But then
he had to have concluded that things
were so bad in 2019 that this this was
it. It was over.
You know
>> why? Why do you say that?
>> Cuz he killed himself.
>> You do believe he did?
>> I do. I believe he killed himself.
>> What makes you believe that considering
all the evidence that they have? See,
but the evidence
the evidence isn't as clear as I think
most people would want it to be. For
example, and I base this on my own
experience in the federal prison system.
>> Mhm.
>> The guards, number one, have their heads
up their asses 24 hours a day. The only
qualification to be a prison guard in
the federal system, the Federal Bureau
of Prisons, is you have to be working on
a GED and no uh felony convictions.
That's it. There's this rule
that prisoners can't touch the mail,
right? So, we have mail call every day
at four o'clock and the guards are
supposed to say your name and hand you
your mail. Most of the time the guards
didn't do mail call. Prisoners did mail
call in violation of the rule of the
rules. Any idea why? Because they
couldn't read.
>> It was as simple as that. The guards
couldn't read basically.
>> Yeah. I mean, they literally could not
read to call out the names. So, number
one, they're idiots. Number two, the
cameras are always broken. Always. I was
a janitor in the uh chapel when I was in
prison. And every day, part of my job
was to go in there and break up guys
having sex in the chapel.
>> In the chapel.
>> Yeah. Because of the Lord.
>> That's what I said. You guys, this is
God's house for heaven's sake.
[laughter]
What are you going to do? But the reason
they would all be having sex in the
chapel is because they knew that the
cameras didn't work. None [laughter] of
the cameras work.
The guards are supposed to be doing
their rounds every 15 minutes or if
there's a suicide watch situation going
on every eight minutes. And with
Epstein, they it was like two hours
before they finally made their rounds.
Why? cuz number one, they're either
jacking off in the uh in the guard
booth, which happens all the freaking
time, or they're sound asleep in the
guard booth, or they're on the phone
with their girlfriends, or they're
surfing the internet. So, no, they don't
they don't make the rounds. And then
people are like, "Oh, but there's a
glitch. You know, there's this one
second glitch." Yeah, because every
night the cameras reset themselves.
They're old cameras. They still use
tape. And they tape over yesterday's.
>> Then why don't they let the guards talk?
Why were the guards like
>> Oh, they would never let the Cuz the
guards are I just stopped myself from
saying a word that's not supposed to be
>> [__]
>> These guys are so stupid.
You know, a a guard from the prison
where I was um emailed me. He he saw one
of the one of the podcasts and he said,
"This is exactly why we wanted to kill
you." And I said, "Bring it, tough guy."
>> Why? He wanted to kill you.
>> Yeah, cuz I say they're morons and
retards and this and that and it's
[laughter] all true. It's true. Learn to
read and then maybe we can have a
conversation.
I mean, otherwise, put up. Let's go. I'm
not afraid of these guys. But this is
why everything went wrong because what
we saw go wrong the night Jeffrey
Epstein died
goes wrong every night. It's the same
thing. But so perfectly like that, you
think it could line up that way?
>> Yes, I saw it. I saw it. For example,
>> not supposed to have microwaves in the
housing unit in it, right?
>> Mhm.
>> And [clears throat] then people are
like, "Ah, you know, you [__] long
enough, they're going to they're going
to put in a microwave." Say, "Put in a
microwave." All right. There was a
serial killer in my unit. And he took a
liking to me inexplicably.
[laughter]
So we called him truck because he was a
long-distance truck driver and he would
murder prostitutes all along his route
and he got caught. [snorts] So
So he would be like, "Hey John, uh he
had these like rotten black little nubs
for teeth." John, uh I saved you a seat
in the TV room. Watch the Steelers game.
I'm like, "Thanks, Truck." Or, "Uh, hey,
there's a new classic rock station. I
know you like classic rock at 1600 a.m.
Thank you, Truck.
Truck hated hated hated pedophiles.
Hated them. Fully a third of the prison
is pedophiles cuz remember they're all
at the low security level,
>> right?
>> So
there's like this rule in prison, no
pedophiles are allowed in the TV room
and pedophiles aren't even allowed in
their own room unless it's to sleep.
Okay? So if you're a pedophile and it's
the middle of the day, get the [__] out
of the room. M well there's a pedophile
in his room [snorts]
and the guy's like blah blah blah blah
blah. He won't stop talking. Well,
another thing is pedophiles aren't
allowed to have any visitors in their
room. So, you can't have another
pedophile because they're going to talk
about pedophilia, which is what they do.
They relive their crimes every single
day. [clears throat]
>> They like they can't help themselves.
>> So, this pedophile is just yapping away.
And Truck is getting angrier and angrier
and angrier.
And finally, the pedophile lays down for
a nap. truck had gone to the commissary
and he bought a bottle of olive oil,
which is $2.85. You can because
everybody cooks in their cells.
>> Plastic or glass?
>> Plastic.
>> So, he pours the olive oil into a bowl
and he microwaves it. So, it's boiling.
Like literally, it's bubbling, boiling,
scalding oil. And he pours it on the
pedophile's face while he's sleeping.
And the guy, the scream, I'll never
forget the scream. and his skin is just
like dropping off of his skull. And
pedophile got a pedophile. The pedophile
got, you know, medevaced to Pittsburgh.
They landed a helicopter in the yard and
medevaced him to Pittsburgh. Truck got
another 10 years onto the 40 he was
already doing for being a serial killer.
>> He was only doing 40 as a serial killer.
>> I know, right?
>> He had a great lawyer.
>> Yeah, he did. But the point is that
there are rules for everything and
nobody pays any attention to them. and
nothing works the way it's supposed to.
>> Then why does the Justice Department
come out and say things like, "Oh,
here's all the evidence." And then they
show that they didn't put all the
evidence. And I'm just talking about
like that.
>> Well, then that proves my point because
people are idiots at every single level.
>> It doesn't matter if you went to Harvard
Law School, you can still be an idiot,
>> right?
>> And another thing, too, this is this is
a lesson that that government officials,
especially senior government officials,
just cannot learn. And it is that the
cover up of the crime is always worse
than the crime.
>> Oh yeah.
>> Always.
>> You know,
>> a lie be gets 10 more lies be gets a
hundred more lies.
>> And Richard Nixon didn't resign because
of Watergate. Richard Nixon resigned
because of the cover up of Watergate.
>> I think it's the same situation here.
>> All right. Well, let me flip it around
on you.
I have always thought
still do think that Jeffrey Epstein is
dead and I feel pretty comfortable.
>> I spoke to his brother recently. I said
I said is he dead?
>> And he's like he's dead. I I identified
the body. I'm just
>> I mean I spoke to OJ. I didn't speak to
him, but he said he didn't do it. You
know what I mean? Like
>> he identified the body. He said I think
he was murdered. And that's a debate,
you know, that he wanted to have with
me. But he said, "Yeah, he's dead. I
identified his body. I took it to the
crematorium.
>> Joseph Scott Morgan, friend of mine,
broke this down. He's a medical death
investigator. He broke it down like
scientifically with all the bones, the
hyoid bone and all that about what would
not make sense about it being suicide
and therefore it being murder.
Obviously, Dr. Michael Boden,
>> who's like the goat with all this,
>> he's the goat,
>> also does not think
>> that he killed himself. So, it's
possible. It's at least possible that he
was killed.
>> It's possible. Definitely.
>> Absolutely.
>> Now, I do think he's dead.
>> Mhm. But again, this whole thing is just
like you you almost have to open your
mind to [__] everything. That's
crazy. So, I'll ask it like this.
If you were tasked, not that you ever
would be, it's hypothetical people, but
if you were tasked with making the world
believe that Jeffrey Epstein was dead
and getting him out of that prison
without anyone knowing to wherever he's
going to go to get [__] facial
surgery and live out his life, how would
you do it? Oh, you would take out the
body, whether it's a a body double or,
you know, made out of silicone or
whatever. Take it out in full view of
everybody. [snorts]
That's how I would do it. Let as many
people as possible see this body
so that reasonable people can agree to
disagree.
>> They did do that.
>> Mhm. And there was a New York Post
reporter very ready to go. And there was
the conversation about the ear, which
I've heard a thousand million times.
>> Those ones I'm always a little skeptical
of because they can doctor them,
>> of course. Well, it's like this stupid
obviously AI generated picture of him
just like walking down the street in Tel
Aviv.
>> Oh, yeah. That one that one's not real.
But I'm saying like So [laughter] the
recipe you just gave me though
>> Mhm.
>> is in line. It's not to say that's what
happened.
>> That's what they did.
>> Yeah. Sure.
>> Yeah. Yeah, cuz I had another guy in
here, Kenneth Gibson, who's worked in
media forever, and he's like, the idea
that a New York Post reporter on an
early Saturday morning in [__] August
was that ready to go immediately after
this?
>> Yeah.
>> Sketchy.
>> And another thing, too, is if I wanted
if I wanted to initiate a cover up of
this scale,
I would
cremate whatever it is I took out on
that gurnie. Because otherwise you'd be
you'd be having people say, "Okay, let's
just settle this. We're going to dig him
up. We're going to get a court order.
We're going to exume the body. We're
going to do DNA testing and make sure
that this is Jeffrey Epstein." Can't do
that. Cremated.
>> I don't know anymore, John. I really
don't. I have to tell you, [snorts] I
was jaded anyway because of my own
personal experience,
>> but now it's like I don't believe
anything anymore. Not at face value
anyway. Have you had your like any kind
of moment where you think back to a
bunch of stuff, different moments and
visions of like things you did that you
were certain were because of one thing
in one way and one person and one
mission that you're now like, "Wait a
minute. Why was that guy there, too?" I
think about that kind of thing all the
time.
>> Yeah, I do. And in some cases, it's
taken years for me to finally conclude
like, "Oh crap, that's what that was
about." Mhm.
>> I've thought about this Rockefeller
thing a million times.
>> Yeah.
>> You know,
>> I I've told you the story. It was the
one and only time I ever received a
phone call from Coen Powell. I told you
the story.
>> I You told the internet in the new voice
as well.
>> Yeah. And in the New Voice, but I think
about that a lot, too.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, and and I remember when it
first happened, I remember thinking,
"This wasn't your fault. Don't let it
bother you." And it's bothered me for
decades.
>> It's human lives. You're a real person.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. The story was that Coen Powell
asked how to target someone in Iraq.
John said what it was and
>> gave him his address
>> and then he found out eight of them got
bombed later. [laughter]
>> There was one time
>> dozens of cruise missiles, you know,
vaporized the building.
>> Every time I watch that clip, I think of
the [__] uh Mark Wahlberg line that
departed. Yeah, it can send a [__]
cruise missile up the ass of a camel
from a thousand yards away. [laughter]
Thousand miles away. Not to get too far
off the topic, but the assassination of
Zawahi, the number two in al-Qaeda.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> You know, we shot him with a with a
drone launched missile, right?
[clears throat] The missile had no
warhead on it, right? We did that on
purpose because we didn't want to kill
the women and children inside the
apartment. He came out onto the balcony
to smoke a cigarette. Fired the missile
at him. It went completely through his
body. A missile went completely through
his body. And with no warhead, there was
no explosion. Can you imagine cleaning
up that mess? [laughter]
[laughter]
I appreciate the uh responsibility on
that one. At least they didn't hit a
wedding.
>> Oh, we did. It
>> was a little better in the Obama.
>> They hit every every wedding during
Obama.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It was uh that was
interesting. But the thing I had wanted
to bring it to when I was bringing up
the early origins of Jeffrey Epstein
with that aly mama deal is obviously
>> the point there is that there is some
sort of relationship with intelligence
intelligences.
>> Absolutely.
>> At the time and there is a tweet to send
it to you. Yep. He has it up. So this is
from Ronald Reagan good
>> about Iran Contra. Okay.
>> In his new auto and this is from back in
the day obviously because he's dead. Uh,
in the new autobiography, former
President Ronald Reagan says Israel was
the instigator and prime mover in the
Iran Contra affair. He blames the
Israelis for misleading him into
believing he was selling arms to
so-called Iranian moderates when some,
quote, may have had links to the
Ayatollah Kameese government and were
trying to obtain weapons under false
pretenses," unquote. Israel began the
arms deals with Iran when it contacted
Robert McFarland, Reagan's national
security adviser, to propose the first
sale and continued to press the secret
dealings thereafter. Reagan writes in an
American life that Prime Minister
Shimone Perez was behind the proposal.
The former president says Iranian
middlemen endorsed by Israel helped
quote win the freedom of three hostages
unquote. Reagan adds, but the same
middlemen behaved at times like bait and
switch conmen with the sole intentions
of proeteers. So with Iran Contra, they
were trying to get weapons to the
Sandinistas in South America. And they
were trying to do it by financing $150
million deal to with through Iran when
we weren't supposed to be dealing with
postrevolution Iran in the 80s. That's
like the very high level version of it.
But
>> it says down here too, Patrick Ali says
that that Epstein was was roommates with
uh with Stanley Pottinger. He was in up
to his neck in Iran Contra. Roommates
partners and roommates with J. Stanley
Pottinger who helped ship weapons to
Iran prior to Iran contract.
>> Can we read this Steve?
>> Good grief.
>> So according to his former friend the
journalist Jesse Cornbluth who's
Epsteined up the ass. Yep.
>> In pause. In the mid 1980s Epstein said
he worked
he worked for governments to recover
money looted by African dictators and
occasionally subcontracted to those same
autocrats to help them hide their stolen
[snorts] money. A source who spoke with
journalist Vicky Ward from Vanity Farah
the 03 piece said one of Epstein's
clients was the late Saudi arms dealer
Hashogi, a middleman in the in the Iran
Contra scandal who helped smuggle cash
for the Marcos family out of the
Philippines. In 1988, Hashogi was
arrested in Switzerland. That's hard to
do. For concealing assets and later
faced fraud and racketeering charges in
the US. He was later acquitted. Must had
a great attorney. That year he sold his
200 He sold his 282 foot yacht to the
Sultan of Brunay who soon flipped it to
Donald Trump. And let's go to the next
one right here. Epstein was fired from
Beer Sterns around the time he met
Douglas Lee who I was telling you about.
Epstein then started a short-lived
partnership with Jay Stanley Pottinger,
a former US Department of Justice
official who was investigated for his
role in dealing arms to the Islamic
Republic of Iran. The Iran Contra affair
appears to be a pivotal moment in in
Epstein's life. Between 81 and 86, the
Reagan administration covertly sold arms
to Iran, which was at war with Saddam
Hussein's Iraq. So, they were selling to
the Iranians they didn't like because
they liked Saddam Hussein even less. My
question is, why is he this didn't
wasn't clocking to me at first cuz I
looked at this very quickly before we
got on air. Why is Reagan saying that
that benefited the Israelis when the
Israelis really don't like the Iranian
regime? Like, that has always been their
big bug. the but the Iranians back then
didn't have a nuclear program and it was
Iraq that was the real like immediate
threat to to Israel because the Iraqis
did have a nuclear program and a
biological weapons program and a
chemical weapons program and they were
working with a Belgian inventor named
Gerald Bull to um to
the the Iraqis were to build something
called the the big gun. This is one of
the very first things I learned about my
first week uh at the CIA. Gerald Bull
created this this giant gun that was so
big you just had to sort of lean the
barrel up against the side of a
mountain, point it in essentially the
right direction and then fire it and it
it would send a shell as far as a
missile would go. And nobody wanted to
buy it. They're like, "What are we gonna
do with this giant gun?" Right? It's as
big as a house. And so the Iraqis said,
"We'll take it." [laughter]
And so the Iraqis bought this thing and
before it kept cracking when when Bull
would would test it, it kept cracking.
So he came up with this idea to put what
he called a condom on the inside of the
gun to smooth the barrel and to and to
keep the the reverberation from the shot
from cracking it. But before he could
test it with the condom inside, the
Israelis assassinated him.
>> They're pretty good at that.
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah. Gerald Bull and his giant gun.
I remember saying to my boss, like I
say, I was only on the job for a week. I
said, "This is a joke, right?" And he
said, "No, no, this is deadly serious.
It's a giant gun. They have to lean it
up on the side of the mountain to fire
it."
>> I'm picturing that thing in Game of
Thrones they were trying to take the
dragon out with where they're just
[laughter]
like, "Come on, baby. Let's go.
>> [laughter]
>> All right. So,
you had always maintained
that Jeffrey Epstein was a massage
access agent.
>> Do you think I wanted to bring this up
first so we at least had the context
what Ronald Reagan said about this.
>> Probably his handler said about it
because I don't think he was all there
by the time he wrote that book.
>> Yeah. Not a chance. So, so do you think
that in something like that, if in fact
the Israelis had an interest in seeing
Iraq be neutralized more, do you think
that this is the prime type of situation
where he could have been recruited at
that time?
>> Absolutely.
>> Yeah.
>> Do you think that's what happened?
>> You know, when you're when you put all
of these episodes together in a line,
that would make sense to me.
>> Yes. Next question.
This is a deal where the CIA is running
a lot of ops as well, meaning they have
to know he's involved with this.
>> You know, that's a good question. He
would have had to have bumped up against
CIA ops people or even if not CIA ops
people, NSC people who were in up to
their necks in this thing.
>> National Security Council.
>> National Security Council, you know, the
likes of of U. As I said, Admiral Po
Dexter, Richard Cord, uh, Oliver North,
all these guys. So, even if if you're
not dealing directly with agency people,
although you probably would be, you're
going to at least be dealing with White
House people.
Now, you had said earlier you never
heard Jeffrey Epstein mentioned at CIA.
You did hear Hashigi mentioned though a
bunch
>> all the time.
>> Hashigi was also like extremely public
for throughout a lot of his life. That's
right.
>> If
seven people from the NSC and CIA
directly dealt or at least bumped into
Jeffrey Epstein during said mission,
Iran Contra, which was a cover up. They
were covering up something they were
doing.
>> That's right. The comp is it reasonable
to say that the compartmentalization
structure of espionage bureaucracy in
the United States government would mean
that those people would chart this maybe
have it in their own files but not
necessarily share it with anybody.
>> Yes. And I could tell you exactly how
that would play out if I were one of the
agency guys involved and I run into this
American guy who's in the middle of it
and he's not with us and he's not with
the White House people then who the hell
is he with? So what I would have done is
I first would have gone to the White
House people and say who's this
American, this Epstein guy, and then I
would have gone to the FBI and say,
"Listen, just so you know, we're doing
this highly compartmentalized top secret
operation. You don't need to know what
it's about, but you do need to know that
there is a private citizen involved
who's an American just so you can start
a file on him just in case this is going
to be a counter intelligence problem for
us in the [clears throat] future.
It doesn't look like that was ever done.
>> I can't imagine why.
>> That was going to be my next question.
What would be something?
>> He had to have had protection at the
White House. He had to have
>> at that time
>> way back then, sometime between 1981 and
198, you know, four or five.
>> All right. Wait a second. That would
make sense for a second. So if he has
protection at the White House, maybe
through a technical intermediary like
Oliver North or something like that.
Exactly.
>> They're doing this under the table. It's
a crime. So, he's gonna be like, it's
more like the mob. Like, all right, I'm
not saying nothing.
>> I know who that guy is, but I can't tell
people I know who that guy is because
then they'll say, "How do you know who
that guy is?" And now we got a problem.
>> That's right.
>> Okay.
>> That's right. See, you know, I had never
thought of that.
>> That's interesting.
>> But now that we're playing it out,
>> Yeah.
>> that makes sense to me.
>> This is why you're here.
>> So, I had always, again, my mind is very
open on all this. I am not married to
any of this stuff. what I had always
thought just very 30,000 foot view in
the air and some people have misheard me
on recent episodes on how I explain this
so I need to do a better job I'd always
looked at it like okay he's working with
MSAD or and you have to say this
>> or with other intelligence organizations
in Israel because they're not the only
one like Jonathan Pard wasn't with MSD
it was with the military
>> right it was military
>> same [__] but different name but MSAD's
an important you know we have what 18
different intelligence agencies right?
You you would think one or two might be
enough, but you think,
>> but I always thought he worked with
them. And then the thing that really
shifted things for Jeffrey Epstein and
his timeline was the I believe September
2002 flight with Bill Clinton, Kevin
Spacy, and Chris Tucker, which made Page
Six. Prior to then, Jeffrey Epstein was
known as a New York City socialite and
not known publicly. He was known on the
socialite circles, which
>> by the way, when someone's known as a
socialite in New York, red flag should
be fine. But he's he's a in this case a
good spy. He's doing all his sick [__]
He's going to the White House 18 times.
No one knows who the [__] the guy is and
everything. And then all of a sudden,
>> boom, flight happens. Page six story.
Then he has to do the interview with
Vicky Ward in March 2003. He's out
there. no coincidence in some ways that
his case starts coming up in '05 in
Florida because he's a known guy in some
respects. And so my thought always was
and if I were a betting man I would have
said it was probably late 90s when
Clinton was still in office. My bet
always was that CIA was asleep at the
wheel. Maybe because of the
compartmentalization we just talked
about. And you know then they probably
find out maybe it's 1996. I'll put a
year on it. 97. They find out so far
this guy's been to the Clinton White
House 15 times maybe.
>> They're like, "Who the [__]
>> is this guy?" And the British lady who's
>> whose dad ran the Daily Mirror and he
started all the [__] peer reviews and
runs all our kids textbooks in America
and got buried on the Mount of Olives in
[__] Israel 5 days after he got
pushed off a boat.
>> Why is this [__] coming in with
the guy who's taking [__] from the
[__] intern,
>> you know? Imagine the stories that you
could piece together if you had
unfettered access just to the visitor
log.
>> Just to that.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Right. So, someone Linda at Langley,
right?
>> Goes, "Wait a minute. We got a problem."
Takes it up the chain of command
suddenly says, "Boss, I don't know who
the [__] this guy is."
>> They then take 10 minutes to look into
it and they're like, "Oh my god, he's
running a [__] pedal ring at the
beest of the Victoria Secret guy in
[__] New York City." And holy [__]
he's involved with Iran Contra. He's
[__] working with MSAD. He seems to
be an intelligence dealer. The [__]
wife, who's not really the wife's a
problem. She's connected up the ass to
all this [__]
>> Oh my god. THEY GOT DIRT ON EVERYONE,
including the current president. This is
a crisis the likes of which if we outed
this, everything could fall.
>> Sounds very familiar today, by the way.
>> Yes, it does.
>> So they say in that moment, now I, you
know, I proposed the New Jersey
solution. I'm like, just [__] blow
his brains out, right? you know, say to
Mad, "What are you going to do about
it?"
>> I know a lot of guys that would do that,
>> right? Okay, good. I don't know where
they were at this time. You know, we
could have called up [__] Vinnie and
Rocco. They didn't take care of
>> mention. Exactly what I was thinking.
>> That's right. But they didn't do that.
And this is what I just always posited.
And it's a theory. I I can't say like,
"Yo, I got evidence this happened." But
I'm like,
>> they looked at it and they said, "Oh
shit." And they go to the guy and they
go, "All right, you know that we know
that you know that we know that you know
that we know what you're doing here. And
you know that we know that you know that
we know that you [__] have been doing
this a long time and you could take down
the whole system if we tell people about
that. And so you know that we know that
you know that we know that now we're in
a Mexican standoff.
>> And so here's the deal. You're going to
have to keep doing whatever it is the
[__] you do. But now you pay a tax.
You're on our soil. You're going to give
us some information, too.
>> And so now what John, what did he foyer?
He foyed the years 2000 to 2014.
Mhm.
>> Pretty interesting to me, I'll say.
>> Am I crazy or am I crazy?
>> No, it's a it's a great catch. And it
also would tend to implicate both the
Bush and the Clinton administrations.
>> That's right.
Sorry. Bush and Obama.
>> Wait, now you Oh, from the years he
foyed. Okay. I thought I thought you
were talking about the backtrack of what
they didn't catch.
>> Now, the backtrack. Now you've convinced
me that this started even earlier than I
thought.
>> Right.
>> I was thinking Clinton, and it's not.
It's earlier.
>> It's earlier.
>> Mhm.
>> There were some files missing,
>> too.
>> Yep.
>> Not Not just the two and a half or three
million. I mean, they're in there, but
did you see the chart of the years that
they're really missing from?
>> Can we pull up that tweet, thief?
>> Just so people can see this.
>> I have to rethink everything. I have to
rethink things that in the past I would
have said were I feel okay about this
take and now I have to look at it and
say Julian that was a ice cold scalding
ice cold if you will take and this is
just one of these things like it is what
it is when I'm wrong I'm wrong this is a
data dump I'm going to simplify this for
you John because there's some more
specific details here but it is showing
basically like if you will a percentage
of data sets from the Epstein files that
are presented over the years and we can
see that there is a massive gap and
basically like you in the chart if you
will between the years of 1999
to 2001 when among other things you had
the tech bubble blow up you had I
believe that's 99 is when the Lewinsky
impeachment trials happening
>> you have the election of 2000 the highly
contested election of 2000 John Kiryaku
where I don't know someone googled this
for me, but I think there was a big
point of contention in Palm Beach County
as it pertains to that election and
that's where one Jeffrey Epstein did
happen to reside. Just just looking at
some things here.
>> And then in 2001,
you have the worst terrorist attack in
United States history in New York and DC
and in the skies over that fell over
Pennsylvania with U93.
>> And suddenly all these files are
missing. But John, we did get an email
from 2003 that slipped through the
cracks.
>> Really?
>> Oh, you haven't seen this one?
>> No, I haven't seen it.
>> So, there's an email thief. Boom. He's
got it. He's all over it. So, this is
from 2003. Someone named Ed Epstein
sends an email to one GMAX Gilen Maxwell
saying, "Any interest in being on the
shadow commission on 911. The membership
list is secret." She responds, "Thanks
for the invite. Unfortunately, I cannot
be on the shadow commission.
>> A shadow commission.
It takes my breath away.
>> Oh my god. This should be the banner
headline.
>> What What do you make of of that?
>> I don't even know what to say.
I mean, nobody believes what the 9/11
commission concluded anyway. That's
right. But the fact that there was a
shadow commission with a secret
membership list
and Galen Maxwell talked about it in
2003.
Why? That's what I want to know.
>> Good question. And it's like this goes
back to a compartmentalization thing
too, John, because what we do have on
the record that we know happened is
somewhere I think it was like July 6th,
2001, maybe like August 11th, the dates
might be slightly off. There are two
meetings that occur at the White House.
One of them with Condisa Rice where CIA
sent literally tenant Kofheer Black and
some dudes who were still like Rich Blee
who's still I think undercover. That's I
think that's a fake name if I remember
correctly where they tell them an
attack's coming. So like when you look
at the whole like well CIA definitely
did the CIA had a lot of incompetence
because they didn't share information
with FBI and there's there's a lot of
issues there and they deserve a ton of
blame but that was the one thing in this
that was always like the canary in the
coal mine for me where I'm like well it
couldn't have been that like they they
had the leadership warning about it. So
>> yeah, they did.
>> You know, maybe it's the White House
that I I don't know. But there's also
advanced knowledge that we know about
from the Saudis who have always been
covered up and we know about with the
five guys from MSAD in [__] Fort Lee
who were videotaping the thing who were
sent back to Israel on November 6th,
2001.
>> That's exactly right.
>> And I know a guy from the office that
arrested them. And to this day, he
wonders why the [__] they didn't get why
the [__]
>> Mhm.
>> So when I see stuff like this, I'm like,
how many countries are involved in this
thing? God, this is bad.
>> And is it even countries versus is it
this trilateral elite just in
[clears throat] general? Like everyone
wants to just immediately say
>> it's Israel, it's Saudi Arabia, it's the
CI. How about all the above
>> who are working for all the above?
>> Mhm.
>> Possible.
>> Possible. Yes. Yes.
Incredible. sickening, I think, is how
what I first said when we sat down to
start talking. This just makes me sick.
I don't even know what to do with them.
Gmax.
>> Gmax
redacted.
>> She must have bcccded him. Jeffrey, why
would it be in the Epstein files? Why
would it be on his computer?
>> I don't know.
>> She BCCed him.
The membership list is secret.
>> She's not even
Was she an American at the time?
>> I don't Did she ever become an American
officially?
>> I don't know. I wonder like we talk
about this small group, you know, you
got the commerce secretary and
transition chair who just Yes.
Maxwell is a naturalized American
citizen.
>> Born in France to British and French
parents and raised in England. She moved
to the United States in 91 following her
father's death. She holds triple
citizenship being a citizen of the US,
UK, and France.
>> Makes sense.
>> Can say that again.
>> Yeah. So,
[clears throat]
>> but not Israel.
>> Yeah.
Man, you have a guy like Le Let who runs
the transition team, is the commerce
secretary, always in Trump's ear
advising him, shares a wall with Jeffrey
Epstein for technically 21 years, but he
claims it was 14 cuz he didn't move in
till 05. Who knows if even that's true.
>> Openly lies
>> on camera just with this dramatic story
about the first and last time I ever
spent time with that man. And then he
said, "So I never dealt with him in
business, socially, or even for
philanthropy." And and what he was
really doing was remembering all the
things he did deal with him on because
now we saw it on the emails of what it
was. But the guy has, as of the time of
this recording on Friday afternoon, he
has not resigned yet.
>> Still doing his job. And also we find
out his sister was one of the founding
members of the Terramar project which
was like Gilen's postJ conviction postJ
is never going to [__] marry me
project that she did pet project that
has something to do with the oceans that
she did a [__] TED talk on.
>> Oh my god.
>> Do these people just all like [__] each
other?
>> They must. They must.
>> I'm glad I don't know people like this.
>> You don't?
>> I don't. No,
no. I would feel dirty all the time.
Well, there's a guy in the middle for
Well, actually, John, we can't forget
this. Did you see what Hillary Clinton
said the other day?
>> Oh, no. What' she say? She said that
they have Can we play the video, De? I
did it in my solo episode. It's coming
out two days before this, but it's worth
repeating because again, we got the
picture of Gilen in the row looking at
Chelsea coming down the aisle at her
wedding. We know about the 25 to 27
flights on the Lolita Express. We got
images of Clinton all with Epstein.
Obviously, the Clintons are their whole
[__] thing as well. On the side, that
doesn't even have to do with Epstein. We
know about the 18 known visits that
happened to the White House.
>> Mhm.
>> And yet he let's let's run it. If
Hillary Clinton says this when asked
about the links between the Clintons and
the Epstein and Epste regret the links
that there have been
>> you know we have no links we have a very
clear record that we've been willing to
talk about which my husband has said he
took some uh rides on the airplane for
his charitable work
>> for charitable work
>> I don't recall ever meeting him uh
>> I did on a few occasions and thousands
of people go to the Clinton Global
initiative. So it to me is not is not
something that is really at the heart of
what this matter is about. They are
accused and in both cases were convicted
of horrific crimes against girls and
women. That should be the focus and we
are more than happy to say what we know
which is very limited and totally
unrelated to their uh behavior or their
crimes and we want to do it in public
because let's make this transparent. The
survivors deserve that. The public
deserves that. But
[sighs]
>> God,
[snorts]
they just lie with straight faces.
>> Straight faces.
>> Mhm. [clears throat] How does a guy like
Jeffrey Epstein get so involved with
with Bill Clinton clearly before he got
into office?
>> Yeah, that's a good question. Could he
have spotted Bill Clinton that early on
in the process? Just another governor?
>> Well, there's a governor who was letting
Barry Seal fly coke planes in Demina
with no questions asked.
>> Yes. Although I always believed he was
told, "Hey, uh, we're going to do this
and you're going to say it's okay." And
he did.
>> What makes you think that?
>> Because that would have been a federal
operation. I mean, we all knew,
everybody knows now that the CIA uh was
was allowing cocaine into the country,
making its way to Los Angeles. Um, so it
would have been federal. It's not up to
a governor to say, "No, no, you can't
you can't do this." It's like, "Shut the
[__] up. We're doing [laughter] it.
We're going to do it and you'll become
president.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Listen to what we say.
>> Exactly.
>> It's just always funny when Hill when
Hillary not funny, but it's kind of sick
when Hillary talks about like women and
victims and stuff like that.
>> God.
>> And then you think about the things that
both of them are actually accused of.
>> Mhm.
>> It's like come on. That's what I mean.
The political opportunism of this that
I'll call out all day. It's like
>> nobody gets a win here. This is
>> No, there are no good guys in this whole
thing. And then, you know, it just makes
me feel that much worse that Virginia Du
Fray uh took her life. I can't even I
can't even fathom the pressure that she
was under, you know, and she kind of
cracked in slow motion. Remember weeks
in advance of her death, she said she
had been like hit by a school bus or
something and
>> I don't remember the whole the whole
story, but
>> she kind of cracked up right in front of
our eyes.
>> Yeah, it's it's suspicious. And
apparently also it does have to be said
her husband did beat her.
>> Yeah.
>> As well.
>> Yep.
>> She had confided that in in Tara Pel
Mary who was a journalist that she
worked with. And so once her family
released photos of her from towards the
end of her life that included like
standing photos of her with bruises all
over her.
>> Tara said that she did. She had promised
obviously not to say anything, but she's
like, "Now that Virginia is deceased and
her family has released these photos, I
do feel like I should also reveal that
her husband
>> beat her all the time." Doesn't mean she
didn't
>> not something fishy there.
>> Sure.
>> You know, she she
>> Yeah, this is bad.
>> She went after a lot of people.
And I just, you know,
it's like these people, they see all
these things 20, 30, 40 years ahead at
their cute little [__] Bilderberg
meetings, but they couldn't see the
internet coming.
>> Yeah. Right.
Yeah, that's right.
>> It's kind of weird, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Mhm.
>> There's a guy that's been at the middle
of all this, Steve Bannon, who I
mentioned, Henry Abbott earlier. Shout
out to Henry for turning me on to this
back in 2021, 2022.
>> And it all turned out to be true. It was
all true. Steve Bannon goes way back
with Leon Black and all those guys. You
can trace it back to the 80s and you can
trace back the earliest investments in
things that became Cambridge Analytica
in 1992. So they were already thinking
about how to influence people through
fear all the way back then, but they
weren't thinking about the very tools
they were building being used against
them to have the public be able to
discuss things in the open, including
the [__] they do behind closed
doors.
>> Imagine why. That doesn't make sense to
me, though. Like, what am I missing
there?
>> You know, one of my favorite movies is
is a 1970s sci-fi film called Soilent
Green.
>> You mentioned it last time. Yep,
>> I did.
>> Mhm.
>> And um Soilent Green takes place in the
in the future. It was filmed in like
or something and I think it takes place
in 2015. and cars, you know, float on
the air and uh the world is overpop
populated and people can't afford food.
And it gives you a pretty good depiction
of
of a world that's on the brink of just
falling apart. The only thing that they
just got completely and totally wrong
was every time Charlton H, the main
character, who's a policeman, every time
he needed to make a call, he'd pull over
to the side of the road, go into a phone
booth, and make the call.
>> I guess there are just some things
people don't see.
>> That's a good way to put it.
>> You know, I remember being I was in a
station in the Middle East. I was there
on temporary duty for a week, week and a
half and there was a tech team in from
headquarters and they were installing
the first ever um email program.
>> And so everybody in the station was
gathered around this computer and
they're showing us that you you click on
this little button that [clears throat]
had an envelope on it and then you write
in somebody's name and hit refresh and
their actual name pops up and then you
can just write them a like a letter.
It's called electronic mail, email. And
the station chief says, "Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Are you saying that my
people can have access to anybody they
want? They just write this electronic
mail and hit send." And the guy said,
"Yes." And the chief said, "I don't like
it. I don't like it one bit."
>> And then he sort of made this edict that
there would be none of this email
in his station. Sometimes you just don't
see it. You just can't. Your brain can't
comprehend it. And maybe that's what
we're looking at here with with our 2020
hindsight.
>> I don't understand though in the 2010s
once it was a real thing like an email.
>> Yeah. Cuz it's like yes, obviously these
people were talking in a way that they
didn't think the DOJ would ever release
their emails to the public,
>> right? But you have people in 2021,
2022, 2023 keeping their jobs and
saying, "No, I regret my relationship,
but I didn't really know them." And now
it comes out that they did. And yet,
maybe I'm thinking of this too simply
and I'm the farthest thing from a
lawyer, but discovery exists. If you get
sued civily and stuff,
>> you get access to everything
>> and that can get leaked.
>> Mhm.
>> So why it often does,
>> right? So these people being so arrogant
>> to be like, "Ah, no one will ever know
that I had 11,500
emails with the dude, so I'll keep my
job at Goldman Sachs." It's just
incredible. Yeah, it's crazy.
>> What goes through somebody's mind like
she knew how many emails I mean, she at
least in her mind had a ballpark figure.
>> Kathy Rumler.
>> Kathy Rumler. How many emails she
exchanged with with Jeffrey Epstein. And
did she think that by not telling the
seauite at Goldman Sachs that it just
wasn't going to be a problem? That this
was never going to come to light? I
mean, the guy died in 2019. It's 2026
and it never occurred to her, you know,
maybe I should try to get ahead of this.
>> This is going to be a problem.
Or was she that arrogant to think that
she could just weather this? H
>> and you know if if you're the CEO of if
you're the CEO of Goldman Sachs, you
have to be saying [__] Rumbler, what
was she thinking?
>> Yeah. I mean, he should have done that
those three years ago.
>> Yeah, he should have. Yes.
>> Should have just cut ties with these
people.
>> Mhm. you know,
like when it when it when they're in
that kind of position, it gets weird
when he's like friends with or
associating with guys in academia and
stuff like that cuz you're like, well,
you know, funders come in and fund
stuff.
>> Mhm.
>> And now we see a lot of that was a lot
closer than that to be clear. But like
when you're a lawyer at the Obama
Justice Department, like the lawyer or
in the Obama White House and you have
that kind of access and you were dealing
with this guy a ton who you know is a
spy now.
Mhm.
You have to know you're going to be
fried in this. It's there's just no way
to look at it. And if you've got the
kind of money that the general counsel
at Goldman Sachs would have, then you
hire a reputation recovery firm, right?
And they're out there, reputation.com
for, you know, average people like you
and me
>> or Peggy Seagull.
>> Or Peggy Seagull
>> and get ahead of this.
>> Yeah.
>> And and I don't think anybody thought to
do that.
>> They did not. Mhm. [clears throat]
And it's very clear that Jeffrey
maintained
all of his power or I should say almost
all of his powerful contacts including
new ones post conviction. You know,
that's the oddest thing to me was that
conviction. This is a child sex crime
conviction.
As
entry level as it was for him because of
the sweetheart deal. You think that that
would send people screaming from the
room and it didn't. It didn't set him
back at all. He just jumped right in.
Right back in. No problem. What do you
think the angle with Bannon was looking
at this? Cuz Bannon leaves the White
House with Trump after he's fired and
then from all the texts we can see,
which are cringe, the emails we can see,
he is essentially becoming that PR guy.
Yeah, he is
>> for Jeffrey Epste. He even has an email
in there where he's like, "You have a
[__] jihad against you." The likes of
which I've never seen and I've seen a
lot of [__] And then, you know, they're
following up emails on here where he's
sending Jeffree articles and saying,
"Well, this makes you sound like you're
contrite." And, you know, talking about
all this stuff and then he films them on
camera for what was reported to be up to
18 hours worth of footage. We have like
2 to four hours of it or something
through the files. You know, this is a
guy Bannon who, like I said, goes way
back to the 80s with all these people.
Is he Is he a spy? Like, I've always
believed that. Do you think that's
plausible?
Plausible? Sure. Likely? I I can't
imagine.
>> Why? Because at the position that he was
counselor to the president, he would
have been vetted, should have been
vetted nine ways from Sunday. He should
have been. The FBI should have been all
over this. Of course, you know my
position on the FBI. So,
um,
>> but Howard, you say that Howard Lmerce
adviser, Leon Black, Leon Black's son
works in the [__] administration.
Like, these are vetting 101.
>> Yeah, you're right. You're right. Sure,
it's plausible. I'm trying to think what
the hook would be, what what the
what the vulnerability would be to
recruit him because Bannon's almost a
billionaire,
>> right? He owns the rights to Seinfeld
and a whole bunch of other things. He's
worth the last I saw several years ago,
he was worth $750 million. So, you're
not going to recruit him with money
>> unless he was recruited before he got
it.
>> Unless Okay, that's a good point.
He always ends up in places. That's the
thing. He's always in the right place.
>> He's long been in the right place at the
right time.
>> There was one phone call I was on with a
guy who was talking my ear off back in
>> that I another one of those like shiver
up the spines cuz this was after I had
read the Abbott piece. I was on to this
with Steve Bannon and this dude was
listing off a whole bunch of things and
he starts talking about this guy Brock,
Mighty Ducks Brock guy. Can we Google
that? Brock uh
>> Brock Pierce.
>> Brock Pierce. You know about Brock
Pierce?
>> No.
>> Brock Pierce is worth a [__] ton of
money. Made it. He was an Mighty Ducks
actor. Ends up I'm going to really
shorten this up for people, but he ends
up in a partnership business-wise with
this guy who ends up having these
parties out in Hollywood where they the
the guy is ising
boys, underage boys.
>> My god.
>> And that ends up coming out and then
they all flee to Spain. That guy ends up
getting arrested. He stands I think he
stands trial or makes a deal or
something and then eventually gets
permission to leave the country for some
sort of surgery and never comes back and
gets a new name.
>> But Barack,
can you pull up as Wikipedia def cuz now
it's in there and this is starting to
like break open. I've been telling
people to pull on this, but go down. Def
Brock ends up up a little more,
more,
more, more. Right. And
up a little more. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. So, Brock ends up founding in
2001. Now, I'm going right off Wikipedia
people. He founded Internet Gaming
Entertainment, a company that pioneered
the MMORPG
currency selling services industry
between 04 and '05.
spent more than $25 million buying out
seven smaller competitors, including
four auction platforms and many fan and
content sites. And in ' 05, PICE
estimated the accounted for about 50% of
this online market in the US, which has
about $500 million in annual volume.
Pierce brought in Steve Bannon, formerly
of Goldman Sachs and Breitbart News, to
seek venture capital, and a deal was
made in February 2006, yielding 60
million, of which Pierce took away 20
million for a minority stake. The next
year, the company faced a class action
lawsuit with no assets. The company
failed, and Pierce was conveniently
forced out. Now go down to the Epstein
section. Def.
In February 2026, an investigation by
the Kev independent and newly released
US Department of Justice documents on
Jeffrey Epstein reported that the files
included an email in which a man
identified his peers described as a
co-founder of Tether told Epste that a
boat in Antigua full of amazing uh
Ukraine's finest was waiting for him. In
a separate analysis of the same document
released by the crypto news outlet
Protos stated that in 2012 after Eptine
asked PICE to take photos and find me a
present during a trip to Moscow, Kev,
and Odessa, which is where they would
source a lot of underage women and
traffic them. By the way, PICE emailed
Epstein's dozens of photographs of a
Ukrainian woman named Anastasia and
closed the message by writing that
Ukraine is now my favorite country. And
in another email, he invited Epstein to
join him on a boat in Antigua, once
again full of Ukraine's finest. This is
stuff that is now new online that I was
told in 2002 directly about this. And
just conveniently, this guy before he
even blows up, he was a Mighty Ducks
actor. Before he blows up as a
businessman and before, like this person
I was on the phone with also told me
about his Jeffrey Epstein connections as
well. before that he just happens to
bring in Steve Bannon to this video game
community that also then this is where
it gets above my pay grade but it has
and pull that mic around because I want
you to say what you're going to say but
it has to do with moving money online
that's like through video game coins
that can be laundered into other stuff.
Maybe people out there can help me but
go ahead.
>> I was going to say because it was a big
thing that China had first gotten
involved with with the video game
Runescape. They'd sell in-game currency
for real money. But this is weird, and
I'm only going to bring this point up
for you to pull on if you want. This
whole conspiracy that they keep seeing
all this activity from Epstein's account
on Fortnite and all these video games.
Just think that's a weird little
connection now to know that Bannon was
involved with that. Just saying. I don't
know.
>> Yeah, that's crazy.
>> It's weird.
>> I don't know, man. And he's still very
much an insider in Washington. He's got
his podcast. He's got a house on Capitol
Hill.
>> Mhm.
>> He's the war room. Yep.
>> Yeah.
>> What do we do?
>> Do you just blow it all up?
>> You know what? We're going to have to
we're going to have to
like even if it means taking to the
streets, demand the release of all the
remaining documents. We have to they
have to be released. First of all, the
law mandates that they be released. It's
not at the Pam body or anybody else.
They have to be released. That's the
law.
And then we need to rely on people like
you
to go through these things and make
sense of them.
How about all the code words they're
using?
>> Yeah. See, you know, that's another
thing. See, and this is we're weakened
by the fact that we can't charge people
with crimes. You know, imagine how easy
how much easier it would be
to say, "Look, you're involved in this.
We've got a conspiracy charge hanging
over you. You're going to do at least 5
years or you can tell us what all these
code words mean and walk us through this
one step at a time and then we'll figure
out, you know, something a little
easier.
But the DOJ can't do that.
There's one that's used in there that
DeF and I were looking at this morning
and you know, your brain runs in a lot
of different directions where it says
jerky.
And there was a guy who did a nice
breakdown of this. Def, let me give you
this, dude. I actually have it right
here. So, I want to give him a shout
out. This is Dr. G Explains
on YouTube. And what I liked is he
didn't he even when it was obvious where
it's like, "All right, we could
definitely make some sort of like this
type of conclusion there." He didn't. He
just reported the [__] emails. But
the way they're they refer to we need
more jerky. We need to put it in the
fridge. We need this number of pounds of
it. We
>> have to cook it. This email right here
pulled up says, "How is your jerky
situation? Should I bring any more?"
Then there's another email to Jeffrey
Epstein from Unknown. Francis has time
to come tomorrow to show me how to make
it. Jerky class, anyone? It will also he
will also bring you a taste of his new
jerky recipe from the restaurant and
sends a warm hello. He is working at a
restaurant called Cannibal and Cooks. Is
this real?
>> This is from Jmail.
Wait for it. Beef jerky and steak. He
has time at 3 p.m. tomorrow if this is
okay with you. And they refer to like,
didn't they refer to storing it like
chemically?
>> No, in freezers.
>> In free. Yeah.
>> That's why I thought blood.
>> Oh man.
>> I mean,
>> see, this is why we need the rest of
these documents. I
>> agree.
>> The whole thing is a 4chan.
>> Yeah. A dream. Yeah, [clears throat]
>> I will freely admit it.
>> You're right.
>> Yeah,
>> they did what?
>> Steve sent me some.
>> There's also an Epstein connection to
the creator of 4chan quote moot
>> and how No, you're good. And how he and
Bannon helped to create
>> politics
>> r/politics which basically create
created the alt-right pipeline that
helped Trump win the election. [snorts]
It just goes deeper and deeper and
deeper. Okay. Can you pull up the Peter
Teal Brexit email exchange?
>> Yeah.
>> With with with Epstein 2016, June 2016.
>> It's probably not in
>> I I have this one about the collapse. Is
that what you're talking about?
>> Yes. Okay. So, Epstein, you know what's
crazy, bro? I remember Oh god, that's so
weird. I remember where I was when this
happened, too. This wasn't that far
away. Okay, so Brexit, he sends to Peter
Teal, Brexit, just the beginning. Peter
Teal responds of what? And Epstein goes,
"Return to tribalism, counter to
globalization, amazing new alliances.
You and I both agreed zero interest
rates were too high. And as I said in
your office, finding things on their way
to collapse was much easier than finding
the next bargain."
This is where the whole bankers
profitering off of war and obviously
Peter Teal is not a banker. Jeffrey
worked in finance for bankers and stuff
but like they're from the banker class
if you will. This is where I look at
that and go well here you go.
>> Wow.
>> Oh my god.
I never seen you so speechless this
much.
>> I feel bad that I'm so shocked that I
can't contribute very much. [laughter]
It's so overwhelming. It's so sickening.
I I didn't realize it was this deep.
Incredible.
And you know, Jeffrey Epstein aside, and
Glenn Maxwell, of course, these are the
people that are still running the
country.
>> Yes.
>> Literally,
>> they're running the economy.
Notice the vice president hasn't said
anything.
>> Not a word
>> recently.
>> Not a single word.
>> That's his chief funer right there.
>> Yes, it is.
>> He also had a
>> He created JD Vance.
>> Yes. But actually before that, are you
aware that JD Vance had a fundraiser
dinner at Les Wexner's house in 2017?
>> That I I was not aware, but that
actually doesn't surprise me.
>> It doesn't?
>> No, because Les Wexner was the guy in
Columbus, Ohio. And if you're a
Republican in Ohio, you need to kiss the
ring.
>> Yeah.
I did not know it though.
>> If remove our own guilt in this for a
second because we definitely have some
that I I do believe and again I'm very
open to changing my opinion on things
but I do believe
>> in this situation CIA and US
intelligence has blood on its hands with
all this. I I just don't see a scenario
where they don't. But you also have
other governments that do as well.
>> Yes.
>> And it's it's multiple. It's an ally
like the UK. Mhm.
>> It's an ally like Israel where we know
Jeffrey had significant contacts
including Ahoud Barack. It also came out
in the emails that the US
>> uh the the Israeli UN security team came
over to install all of his security at
his place. Oh, you didn't see. Can we
pull up this email, Dave?
>> Are you kidding me?
>> John's having a [__] crisis of
conscious right now. I'm sorry.
>> There's been a lot of me talking the
last half hour while John's just like
questioning everything. [laughter]
All right. So, this is from Mario Nall.
Israeli government installed
>> Oh, I just talked to Mario two days ago.
>> Yeah, there you go. What is the chances?
Israeli government installed security
systems Epstein's Manhattan building
where he housed underage models starting
2016. Israeli mission to the UN
coordinated with Epstein's staff to
install alarm sensors and surveillance
equipment. Rafi Schlommo, you know, I
said this earlier, very Russian name.
Head of security for former Israeli PM
Ahoud Barack personally controlled
access to the apartment. did background
checks on cleaners, remotely disabled
alarms when people needed to enter, and
Epstein personally improved it all. The
emails are right there. I read these in
the solo episode the other day, but this
this tweets up on the screen. Just if
you wouldn't mind, DeF just pulling up
the email so people can see it.
>> But this is the back and forth. And then
the other one, I think also this is
where they're going through the details.
But then this is where it's laid out
with the Hood's name in there and
everything. I believe Neilia [snorts]
Hood was on the other email, his wife, I
assume. But they're going through the
whole things of what they're going to be
wiring and it seems like they have a
pretty chummy relationship.
>> It sure seems that way. And Jeffrey
doesn't mind holes in the walls. Of
course, we learned that in spades at the
island house.
>> Wow, man.
>> Did you see Netanyahu's
response to
>> no
>> the bar? I'd love to hear it.
I'm paraphrasing here, but he said this
actually proves that we are not guilty
because Audac has attempted to overthrow
the entire Israeli order as a political
opponent for many years and operated. I
don't know if he said in like the George
Soros crowd or something like that, but
he was like insinuating like, you know,
anti-Israel. And we're talking about a
dude to Hub Barack who does have
opposite politics in many cases.
>> Yeah.
>> To Netanyahu except in the case of you
know trying to grow Israel which you
know that's that's what they're trying
to do. How they do that is certainly the
question. But you know
>> to say that about a dude who is like
within Israel a legendary special forces
guy.
>> Yeah.
>> Who got it? We have that the [__] New
York City shot from the movie Munich
right there where he gets a shout out in
the [__] movie while they're doing
while Msada is doing some of the [__]
right?
>> And then he becomes prime minister
eventually, defense minister and
everything,
>> but being with Epstein is a way to show
that you're innocent. That seems a
little
>> Yeah, he's flailing around,
>> right?
>> Unbelievable. Is it an uncservivable
because of the public's reaction if that
information were flatout confirmed by
both governments? Is it an unservivable
act for an allyship between the two
nations? If
>> No,
>> it's not.
>> No. No. This is going to be a little
blip, a temporary blip. Oh, listen.
The Israelis,
the the pro-Israel lobby, mostly in the
form of Apac, is so entrenched in
American politics, American society,
American culture, that the relationship
isn't changing at all. It's only because
of the likes of of Tucker Carlson,
people with large followings out there
speaking truth and talking about what
America first really means
>> that might make a difference. People are
going to they're going to say, "Oh, well
that Barack Well, first of all, he's a
hasband. Secondly, h you know, that was
a long time ago. It's almost 10 years
ago and it's not Netanyahu. Netanyahu is
the one in charge now." That's going to
be the reaction.
But the public is so aware of some of
these things though now because many
people on the left and right it's a very
bipartisan thing
>> very much so. Yes. And so you think even
in this kind of year it would be a blip
if we found out that had some sort of
confirmation that the most prolific
known public pedophile spy dude arms
dealer trilateral commission person
Coney Island resident you know
>> was running a msad honeypot operation
with all the above and money laundering.
>> We just move. They they didn't they
didn't care for more than a few weeks
when Jonathan Pard was caught red-handed
and they were managing the operation
from the Israeli defense minister's
office.
>> Rafi was overseeing it, I believe.
>> Right. Um it didn't matter and the
Israelis hemmed and hod and then kind of
quietly apologized and everything just
kind of roared right back. And I think
that's we're going to see again. So,
here's the other thing a lot of people
say online, and I and I understand why
they say it, but I have you in the
studio right now as someone who used to
be in the intelligence community who can
speak to this, but people will often say
CIA equals MSAD, MSAD equals CIA.
>> It's just simply not true.
>> Okay. And that that's a statement made
out of ignorance.
>> Yeah.
>> Now, why why do you say that?
>> Because I agree with you from what
you've told me, but I'd love for you to
explain it to everybody.
>> The Because the Mossad actively spies on
the United States. Actively.
Yes, we have a close operational
relationship with Mossad. But to say
we're two peas in a pod like that,
absolutely not true. We are with the
Brits, the Canadians, the Australians,
the New Zealanders, the Five Eyes
countries. We have very close relations
with several other, you know, NATO
countries. But the Israelis, listen, at
the CIA,
Israel was ranked as critical threat for
counter intelligence along with Russia,
China, Cuba, and North Korea.
Yeah, the Israelis are not our friends.
They actively recruit Americans to spy
on Israel's behalf to betray the United
States. Now, the people who make those
arguments though, one place where I
could see from their lens is when you
look at the top of the chain would say
directors of these agencies who are
political appointees. You have a guy
like Mike Pompeo who ran CIA who could
not possibly be more pro-Israel, right?
>> Not possible to be more pro- Israel than
Mike Pompeo. So is it possible that
there are some pockets
>> where there is some overlap but for the
most part as you're saying the rank and
file and people who work at the agencies
they don't really like each other.
>> Sure. Yeah. It's it's possible to say
that and you know presidents come and go
administrations change the the
relationship is is you know
fraternal
>> right
>> at the working level it's not so nice.
Mhm. [clears throat]
>> The last thing today, John, this this
has been good, but I know that some of
this is like
>> I'm intellectually exhausted now. I'm
very upset by all this.
>> I can see. [laughter] So, I I I don't I
don't want to
>> It's like what happened to our country?
>> I don't want to torture you,
>> but I do have to get to the one thing
that we left off from the beginning,
which is what you heard about the whole
Iran thing. I'm not going to say
anything. I'm just going to let you go
with whatever you're allowed to say. So,
I have I have a friend uh former CIA
officer who was at the White House this
morning talking to his friends and he
says that a decision has been made to
attack Iran on Monday or Tuesday. The
president yesterday gave the Iranians 10
days to uh to you know accept our
proposals for an end to their ballistic
missile program, an end to to uh their
uranium enrichment program, an end to
supporting um groups in the Middle East
like Hamas and Hezbollah and the
Houthis.
But he's done this before. Well, he
he'll give you 10 days, he'll give you
two weeks, and then he'll just attack
two days into it. He thinks that that
keeps people off balance. Um, the USS
Abraham Lincoln has been in the Arabian
Sea for weeks. We've got about two dozen
support ships in the Persian Gulf, the
Arabian Sea, the Red Sea, and the
Eastern Mediterranean. We've got the USS
Gerald Ford, which is in Gibralar right
now. It's it's passing through the
Straits of Gibralar like today on its
way to uh the Eastern Mediterranean and
probably through the Sewish Canal into
the Red Sea. So we've we're going to
have enough assets to attack Iran in the
next couple of days. And so he said that
there are battle lines that the anti-
>> war forces are JD Vance and Telles
Gabbard. He said that the pro that's it.
He said the pro-war people are led by
Marco Rubio and include Pete Hegsth and
now the joint chiefs of staff. And I I
stopped him on that point this morning
and I said, "Wait a I said during the
Iraq war, at the start of the Iraq war,
the most stridently anti-war
component was the joint chiefs of staff.
They were always the last ones that
wanted to attack because they know what
war is. And he said, "Ah, but you forget
Trump has replaced all of the joint
chiefs this year, this past in the past
12 months," which I had forgotten. any
of these four-star generals who, you
know, had worked their way up through
the ranks but had served under Biden, he
fired all of them. All of them. And he
promoted people that he knew would be
politically loyal.
>> So I, you know, Julian, I I've always
been one of these glass half full guys.
I'm I'm
>> Me, too. I've always been optimistic
about things and I've been saying a lot
in my own podcasts in written pieces.
You know, we we went through round one
with the Omanis and Muscat. We went
through round two with Swiss in Geneva.
Both sides came out and said, "These
were both productive uh meetings. We're
going to go to round three. Everything's
looking good. The Omanis are asking us
to just relax and let them do what
they're good at." The Omanis are really,
really good at diplomacy. really good.
They're very, very good friends.
>> Um, and they're honest. So, the Iranians
trust them as well. And I think that
none of that really matters right now. I
think a decision's been made.
>> Do you think this is to distract from
the current scandal?
>> Uh, probably in part. Yeah.
>> How about them saying they're going to
release the UFO files last night, which
I've wanted released forever, but
>> I know, right? I mean, we've been
talking about this for years.
>> The timing.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> [sighs]
>> Yep.
>> Same movie over and over again.
Different actors just rem.
>> And you remember, you're probably a
little bit too young, but in the ' 90s,
the movie Wag the Dog was like, you
know, people had their hair on fire. Oh
my god, that look, this movie is about
the president made a war to distract
from his affair. It's like, yeah, how
[clears throat] quaint that is now.
>> So quaint.
That seems to be all that happens. And
people have short memories. Mhm.
Well, I hope that I I will take that
clip and put that out tomorrow,
Saturday,
>> so that we can
>> maybe get some attention on that to see
if somehow that little ripple ends up
making its way to change some decisions
cuz
>> one of the promises of of of Trump's
campaign was no more endless wars,
right?
>> Going into Iran is entirely different
than going into Venezuela. 92 million
people. It's a gigantic country. It's
bigger than Texas and it has 92 million
people. And I think that at the White
House, they have just they have just
bitten right into this Israeli
propaganda, the same kind of propaganda
we got in 2003, that as soon as we cross
that border, they're going to throw
flowers at us and they're going to greet
us as liberators and we're all going to
live happily ever after and everybody's
going to get rich on the new oil deals.
And that's just not going to happen. It
never happens.
>> Crazy world, John.
>> It is, man.
Well, I'm sorry to blow your mind a few
times today.
>> I was I'm not often stunned into
speechlessness.
>> You also blew my mind as regular,
though. That happens every single time.
Like you just say, your life experiences
are insane. And I'm really, you know,
jokes aside with the memes. I'm so happy
to see you
>> getting the attention you deserve and
have deserved for a long time for people
that
>> are just learning about John online.
your story had a long very unfair
downswing to it that you know
>> it's been an odyssey that's for sure
>> getting back we all get a good laugh you
know out of these memes but this this
was deadly serious
>> Oh yeah no doubt about it but I'm I'm
really happy to see it and we'll
continue supporting it here
>> good to see you again
>> it's great see you as always sir
>> thank you
>> all right
>> take care
>> everybody else you know what it is give
it a thought get back to me hopefully
we're not at war with [__] Iran peace
>> thank you as always for watching this
video guys if you have not already
subscribed please hit that subscribe
button as well as that like button
Before you leave, see you for the next
episode.